eathealthysecrets.com 2011-06-18

# Privacy Policy | The Diet Solution Program

LIVE SMART SOLUTIONS, LLC, a Nevada limited liability company (“LIVE SMART  
SOLUTIONS”)  is engaged in the business of selling the The Diet Solution Program  
Products and distributing information in the form of newsletters, current research,  
and articles and selling e-books, audios and videos (“Products”) associated with nutrition, diet, health and overall well-being through its web site [  
http://www.beyonddiet.com](http://www.beyonddiet.com/) (the  
“Web Site”). Therefore, routinely, in the course of business, LIVE SMART  
SOLUTIONS may receive personally identifiable information such as your email address  
in addition to other information secured by our service providers such as your credit  
card, telephone number and address (“Personal Information”). In an effort  
to secure our customer’s trust and confidence, we have taken various measures  
to protect your privacy relating to you and your transactions conducted on our Web  
Site, or through any of our active service providers, such as Clickbank.com (“Affiliate”).  
Clickbank.com is a third party online retailer specializing in digitally delivered products that accepts all online  
product orders for LIVE SMART SOLUTIONS as more specifically described below (see  
Third Party Financial Institutions & Affiliates).

This Privacy Policy describes the Personal Information we obtain from you, what  
we do with your Personal Information, the safeguard measures we, or our Affiliate  
has in place to protect it, and to what extent you can control our use of such Personal  
Information. By using the Web Site, the user agrees, without limitation or qualification,  
to be bound by this Privacy Statement.

When you provide Personal Information to our Web Site, you hereby consent to the  
manner in which LIVE SMART SOLUTIONS and its Affiliate collects, manages, protects,  
and discloses your Personal Information in accordance with the terms and conditions  
of this Privacy Policy.

**Third Party Financial Institutions and Affiliates**

When you purchase e-books, audios and videos on our Web Site, you must submit payment information directly  
to Clickbank, including your credit or debit card number, as well as your zip code.  
Such information may be recorded and filed by Clickbank to fulfill your orders.  
In addition, when you return previously purchased products or request a refund or  
exchange, you may be asked to give your name, address,  and other identifiable  
information. Clickbank collects this information to prevent fraud and identity theft.  
If a user contacts any employee or affiliated person, a record of that correspondence  
may be kept.

**Passive Collection of Personal Information**

LIVE SMART SOLUTIONS reserves the right to passively collect information related  
to usage of its Web Site such as time spent on the Web Site, areas visited, and  
sites linked to and from the Web Site. Please be advised that the Web Site may collect  
additional information and may install cookies on members’ hard drives. The  
use of cookies will allow us to improve our Web Site based on the user’s preferences  
and is a widely used industry practice of online businesses. However, the cookies  
are stored on the user’s computer, not on our Web Site. If you do not wish  
to receive cookies, or would like notification of when they are placed on your computer,  
you may set your browser accordingly, if permitted.

**Security of Personal Information** :

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect against  
unauthorized access, use, modification and disclosure of Personal Information in  
our custody and control. We are committed to employing reasonable technology in  
order to protect the security of our Web Site. However, even with the best technology,  
no web site is 100% secure. We will take reasonable measures which we believe are  
appropriate to protect your Personal Information from loss, misuse, alteration or  
destruction, and, where possible, will ask that any third parties to whom we may  
transfer such information to take comparable steps to protect that security.

**Usage of Personal Information**

Your use of this Web Site constitutes your acceptance of the terms and conditions  
of this Privacy Policy.  In accordance with this Privacy Policy, your Personal  
Information may be used for record keeping, to improve the content of our Web Site,  
to customize the site to your preferences, to communicate information to you (if  
you have requested it), site management, fulfillment of requested purchase orders,  
and marketing and research purposes to those who have consented to such marketing.

**Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties**

LIVE SMART SOLUTIONS will not disclose Personal Information collected from users  
of the Web Site to third parties, except to companies with which the Web Site is  
actively affiliated, to contractors we use to support our business (technical support,  
delivery services, and financial institutions, such as ClickBank) whereby we will  
require such third parties to treat such Personal Information in accordance with  
this Privacy Policy, and in connection with the sale, assignment, or other transfer  
of the business of this Web Site to which the information relates. LIVE SMART SOLUTIONS  
may hire third parties to review certain Personal Information to advise it on demographic  
and marketing related issues, but only after such third parties have agreed to maintain  
the confidentiality, security, and integrity of any Personal Information contained  
in accordance with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

**Other Uses of Personal Information**

LIVE SMART SOLUTIONS also uses Personal Information, including information provided  
to us from our service providers, to continually assess and improve the products  
and services we offer. To serve you better, we may combine the Personal Information  
that you give us with publicly available information and information we receive  
from or cross-reference with our marketing partners and others. We use that combined  
information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us, to communicate  
with you about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other  
promotional purposes.

**Promotional Information and Marketing Materials**

We would like to inform you of products and services, sales and special offers that  
might benefit you. You will have the opportunity to sign up for e-mails about our  
products, services, sales and special offers.

if you have provided us with your name and email address. If you would like to stop  
receiving such promotional information from our Web Site, There is a link at the  
bottom of email correspondence, which allows you to Opt-Out of receiving further  
correspondence.

**Disclosures of Personal Information in Legal Proceedings** : If LIVE  
SMART SOLUTIONS, its service providers or its Affiliate are requested by law enforcement  
officials or judicial authorities to provide Personal Information on individual  
users, LIVE SMART SOLUTIONS or the applicable third party provider may,, without  
your consent, provide such information. In matters involving claims of personal  
or public safety, LIVE SMART SOLUTIONS, or the applicable service provider may provide  
your Personal Information to appropriate authorities without your consent or court  
process. LIVE SMART SOLUTIONS or its service providers also will provide your Personal  
Information in response to a search warrant or other legally valid inquiry or order,  
or to an investigative body in the case of a breach of an agreement or contravention  
of law, or in litigation involving LIVE SMART SOLUTIONS, the applicable service  
provider, or otherwise as required by law. We may also disclose Personal Information  
to assist in debt collection where you owe a debt to us.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

If this Privacy Policy is modified, the revised policy will be posted on this site  
within a reasonable time. Please check this Web Site periodically, specifically  
before you provide any Personal Information. This Privacy Policy was last updated  
on January 22, 2009.

**Application of United States Law**

The Web Site is intended for users from the United States and those not governed  
by privacy policies of other countries. Users from the European Union are advised  
not to disclose Personal Information to us. Information sent to us will be housed  
on servers in the United States. Do not submit your Personal Information such as  
your name and email address unless you consent to the application of U.S law and  
to the use and disclosure of your information consistent with this Privacy Policy.

**Access to Personal Information by Companies that Work with or on Behalf of LIVE  
SMART SOLUTIONS LLC.**

Some of our operations, such as our electronic commerce, may be managed by service  
providers who are unaffiliated companies. These companies may share Personal Information  
with their affiliates and with service providers whom they engage to perform services  
related to our Web Site or the operation of our business. Examples of these services  
include payment processing and authorization, fraud protection and credit risk reduction,  
product customization, order fulfillment and shipping, marketing and promotional  
material distribution, web site evaluation, data analysis and, where applicable,  
data cleansing. These companies may have access to your Personal Information on  
a confidential basis only to the extent necessary to perform their functions. In  
no event will we authorize these companies to use your Personal Information for  
any reason other than to provide you with those specific services.

**Privacy Preferences / Opt-Out** : The Web Site offers users the ability  
to opt out of receiving further email updates on fitness, nutrition, and exercise  
by clicking on a link where you can change your preferences to receive or not receive  
marketing, newsletter, and informational materials. You may update these preferences  
at any time. You may also change your marketing preferences or remove yourself from  
our mailing list by clicking on an “unsubscribe” hyperlink contained at  
the bottom of the promotional emails we send to you.

**Our Privacy Statement and Outside Links** : This Privacy Policy only  
applies to this Web Site. Our Web Site may include links to the web sites of our  
business partners, vendors and advertisers. These other sites are outside of our  
control. Please be aware that these websites may collect information about you,  
and operate according to their own privacy practices which may differ from those  
contained in our Privacy Statement. Please read carefully that web site’s own privacy  
policy, as once you are leave our Web Site, any information you submit is no longer  
in our control.

**Contacting Us** : If you have any questions concerning our Privacy  
Policy, a member (or any other user of this Web Site) you may contact us at: LIVE  
SMART SOLUTIONS, LLC with its principal address located at 3405 Salterbeck Street Suite 200D Mt. Pleasant, SC 29466,  or via email at info [at] beyonddiet.com.

LIVE SMART SOLUTIONS LLC

3405 Salterbeck Street Suite 200D

Mt. Pleasant, SC 29466

Last Updated: January 22, 2009

Copyright © 2008  All rights reserved.
